[MUSIC PLAYING]
Enrolling in Amazon brand registry
gives you more control over your product detail pages.
You'll also become eligible for benefits
like stores, A+ content, Sponsored Brands campaigns,
brand analytics, and more.
Use these tools to improve your brand's performance
in the Amazon store.
Requesting selling benefits is different from applying
to sell branded products.
If you're not associated with a registered brand,
you may need to complete a separate application process
to match offers to brand product detail pages.
For information about completing a selling application,
go to Apply to Sell a Product Category or Brand
in Seller University.
If you're an Amazon seller who has a relationship
with a registered brand, you can request a selling role.
It defines the relationship you have with the brand,
either as a brand representative or reseller.
These roles grant different access and privileges.
The brand representative role is for individuals internal to
and directly employed by the brand.
It allows you to access tools that contain potentially sensitive
information about the brand.
The reseller role is for external third-party sellers.
They have access to only a few selling benefits
in order to protect the brand's private information.
You can request either role,
depending on your relationship with the brand,
through the Eligible Brands tab
on the Brand Benefits Eligibility page.
If you can't access the Brand Benefit Eligibility page,
contact the brand's administrator in brand registry.
After requesting a role, you'll receive a notification
that lets you know if the brand administrator
has approved your request.
If approved, you can access related benefits within 48 hours.
For more information about selling benefits,
review the Brand Registry Selling Roles Help page
in Seller Central.